NAA Additional Records 6004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Deceased members before 7/1/96 A-La. (Box 17)
  - Glenn J. Donaldson, 1952-1967 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Zenas Clark Dickinson, 1954-1961 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Charles T. Douds, 1963-1982 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Paul H. Douglas, 1965-1976 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Frank P. Douglass, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - James T. Dunne, 1964-1986 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Harold T. Dworet, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Prof. Theodore Dyke, 1972-1987 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Shelden D. Elliott, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Joseph B. English, 1960-1974 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Harry G. Erbs, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Robert I. Feinberg, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Nathan P. Feinsinger, 1954-1984 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Emmitt Ferguson, 1953-1963 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - John A Fitch, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - E.J. Fosythe, 1961-1985 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Howard G. Gamser, 1956-1974 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Harold M. Gilden, 1979-1985 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - William Gomberg, 1960-1985 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Nathan Green, 1970-1971 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - William P. Halloran, 1963-1975 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Charles G. Hampton, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Paul D. Hanlon, 1964-1986 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Frederick H. Harbison, 1967-1976 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - J. Hazen Hardy Jr., 1953-1985 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Raymond F. Hayes, 1959-1983 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Paul M. Hebert, 1961-1977 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - William M. Hepburn, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Judge David Ralph Hertz, 1971-1984 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Elmer E. Hilpert, 1953-1975 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Henry W. Hoel, 1960-1972 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - John A. Hogan, 1955-1987 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - J. Fred Holly, 1955-1985 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - John Perry Horlacher, 1953-1981 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Guy L. Horton, 1977-1981 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - Aaron Horvitz, 1958 (Box 17, Folder 72)
  - Willard Hotchkiss, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 73)
  - Robert L. Howard, 1956-1973 (Box 17, Folder 74)
  - Andrew Jackson, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 75)
  - Samuel H. Jaffee, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 76)
  - Jules J. Justin, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 77)
  - David L. Kabaker, 1963-1983 (Box 17, Folder 78)
  - Richard W. Keefe, 1974-1980 (Box 17, Folder 79)
  - Edward L. Keller, 1964-1975 (Box 17, Folder 80)
  - John O. Keller, 1954-1963 (Box 17, Folder 81)
  - Louis C. Kesselman, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 82)
  - Ralph E. Kharas, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 83)
  - Howard Kleeb, 1970-1980 (Box 17, Folder 84)
  - David R. Kochery, 1964-1967 (Box 17, Folder 85)
  - Michael J. Komaroff, 1950-1963 (Box 17, Folder 86)
  - Daniel Kornblum, 1958-1979 (Box 17, Folder 87)
  - Bernard P. Lampert, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 88)
  - Jerome J. Lande, 1954-1974 (Box 17, Folder 89)
  - John A. Lapp, 1954 (Box 17, Folder 90)
  - Bora Laskin, 1963-1974 (Box 17, Folder 91)
  - John Day Larkin, 1974-1986 (Box 17, Folder 92)
- Deceased members before 7/1/96 Le-Z. (Box 18)
  - Paul N. Lehoczky, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - John W. Leonard, 1967-1973 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mabel Leslie, 1960-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Robert M. Leventhal, 1979-1991 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Jerome A. Levinson, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Charles H. Livengood Jr., 1954-1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Frederick R. Livingston, 1957-1986 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Charles Loring, 1953-1961 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - William N. Loucks, 1977-1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - James R. Lucas, 1976-1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Marlyn E. Lugar, 1974-1989 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Edward A. Lynch, 1958-1979 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Douglass B. Maggs, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - John M. Malkin, 1969-1984 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Robert E. Mathews, 1972-1983 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Whitley P. McCoy, 1954-1971 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Robert G. Mcintosh, 1957-1982 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Wayne L. McNaughton, 1960-1982 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Arthur J. Meyer, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - David P. Miller, 1953-1976 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Wayne Morse, 1963-1974 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Maurice E. Nichols, 1963-1979 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - (Mr.) Allison E. Nutt, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Member-Designate - Deceased Richard P. O'Connell, 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Samuel James Ogilve, 1965-1973 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Harry H. Platt, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Paul Prasow, 1954-1975 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Leroy Anthony Rader, 1953-1961 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Alexander E.J. Rolston, 1949-1955 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - H. Herman Rauch, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - B. Meredith Reid, 1954-1982 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Benjamin C. Roberts, 1965 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Raymond R. Roberts, 1976-1985 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Joseph Rosenfarb, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Samuel A. Rosenberg, 1964-1974 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Arthur M. Ross, 1967-1970 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Meyer S. Ryder, 1953-1987 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Irving H. Sabghir, 1972-1986 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Woodrow J. Sandler, 1976-1985 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Carl R. Schedler, 1955-1965 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Israel Ben Scheiber, 1954-1987 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Milton H. Schmidt, 1958 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Harold A. Seering, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - B.M. Selekman, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Joel Seidman, 1966-1977 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Peter Seitz, 1958-1983 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Harry Seligson, 1955-1979 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - John F. Sembower, 1953-1982 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Irving R. Shapiro, 1950-1976 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - I.L. Sharfman, 1954-1969 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Harry Shulman, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Morton Singer, 1955-1969 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Alfred T. Singletary, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Summer L. Slichter, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Livington Smith, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Gerald G. Somers, 1961-1978 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Hugo Sonnenschein Jr., 1947-1981 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Joseph G. Stashower, 1954-1966 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Abram H. Stockman, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - George E. Strong, 1955-1960 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - John F. Sullivan, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Charles P. Taft, 1975-1982 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Harry D. Taft, 1953-1954 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - George W. Taylor, 1954-1972 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Maurice S. Trotta, 1954-1976 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Burton B. Turkus, 1953-1982 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Frank R. Uible, 1947-1974 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - Herbert S. Unterberger, 1956-1979 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Clarence M. Updegraff, 1954-1979 (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - James C. Vadakin, 1960-1982 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - Quentin C. Vines, 1953-1971 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Horace C. Vokoun, 1955-1962 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - Robert J. Wagner, 1954-1983 (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Saul Warren, 1954-1965 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Leo W. Walsh, 1965-1985 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Edgar L. Warren, 1954-1955 (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - Charles W. Webster, 1960-1969 (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Allan Weisenfild, 1971-1985 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Martin A. Wersing, 1953-1973 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Dan A. West, 1953-1963 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Robert H. Wattach, 1951-1964 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Thomas P. Whelan, 1956-1979 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Dudley E. Whiting, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - James J. Willingham, 1962-1976 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Edwin E. Witte, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - James H. Wolfe, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 86)
  - David A. Wolff, 1954 (Box 18, Folder 87)
  - Sidney A. Wolff, 1955-1982 (Box 18, Folder 88)
  - Stanton W.B. Wood, 1960-1976 (Box 18, Folder 89)
  - H.D. Woods, 1955-1983 (Box 18, Folder 90)
  - Leslie E. Woods, 1966-1986 (Box 18, Folder 91)
  - Ralph J. Zeigler, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 92)
- Rejected applicants before 1987 A-La. (Box 19)
  - B.M. Becker, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Belkin, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - J. Berkman, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Herbert Nelson Bernhardt, 1983-1986 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Daniel K. Boone, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Myles S. Boothe, 1958-1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - I.R. Broadwin, 1948 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - S. Eugene Bychinsky, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Ralph Campbell, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Bernard H. Cantor Esq., 1966-1977 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - J. Willard Carpenter, 1957-1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Steven A. Carter, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Paul A. Cassady, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Milan T. Chance, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Joseph Chandler, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Jack M. Chapman, 1969-1971 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Kenneth Cloke, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Bernard S. Coleman, 1956-1957 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - H. Raymond Cluster, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - John B. Criswell, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Jack F. Culley, 1977-1978 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Leonard H. Davidson, 1964-1966 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Jack G. Day, 1956-1974 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Robert T. Drake, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Warren James Bardley, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Norman N. Eiger, 1979-1980 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Walter Frederick Eigenbrod, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - L. Whiting Farinholt Jr., 1967 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Ogden W. Fields, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Howard M. Golob, 1981-1985 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Ralph M. Goren, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Bertram Gorrlieb, 1977-1982 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - John A. Griffin, 1959-1960 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Dr. Keith Groty, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Kurt Hanslowe, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - J. Harris Bennie, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Philip Harris, 1965 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Prof. Lafayette G. Harter, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - George F. Hayes, 1957-1965 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Clark Hazelwood, 1966-1968 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - John S. Herrick, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Dr. Hertz, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - William W. Hodges Esq., 1977 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Miles E. Hoffman, 1948-1953 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Robert E. Howard, 1982-1983 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Eugene H. Hughes, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - John E. Hutchinson, 1965-1967 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Joseph Alton Perkins, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Alton L. Jones, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Harry E. Jones Jr., 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Lewis B. Kaden, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Charles M. Kaiser, 1968-1976 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Lawrence Kanzer, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - David M. Kaplan, 1972-1974 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Kenaston V. Wayne, 1974-1982 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - David Tinsley Kennedy, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Leo V. Killion, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Cralile E. King, 1982-1984 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Harold Kramer, 1962-1985 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Leo Kramer, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Samuel Krimsly, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Julius E. Kuczma, 1948-1974 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Tony Driggins, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - A.C. Lappin, 1953 (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Bruce B. Laybourne, 1972-1975 (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - Joseph Lazar, 1963-1966 (Box 19, Folder 66)
- Rejected applicants before 1987 Le-Z. (Box 20)
  - Hiram Lesar (Dean), 1966-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Samuel Levitt, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Bernard Levy, 1977-1980 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Robert Littler, 1962-1963 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Robert B. Lubic, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Garth L. Mangum, 1978-1986 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Irving R. Markowitz, 1962-1965 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - W. Steward Martin, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Daniel E. Matthews, 1981-1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Prof. Royal Mattice, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Edward C. Maxwell, 1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Frederick W. McKone Esq., 1974-1978 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Charles R. Milentz, 1972-1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Max J. Miller, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Preston J. Moore, 1963 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Raphael Henry Morvant, 1955-1956 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Ben Nathanson, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Thomas Fair Neblett, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Melvin L. Newmark, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Padraig O'Donoghue, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Richard A. O'Neill, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Fidelis Rev. O'Rourke, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Hyman Parker, 1954 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Egon Parker, 1965-1966 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Prof. Leo S. Rayl Jr., 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - James J. Reilly, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Reed C. Richardson, 1960 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Albert W. Rill, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Robert C. Roadley, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Thomas Robert, 1963-1966 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - David K. Robinson, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - James W. Robinson, 1972-1973 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Prof. Eleanore J. Roe, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Benjamin Rosayn, 1972-1978 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Sol Rosen, 1964 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Morris S. Rosenthal, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Prof. Howard R. Sacks, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Mr. Raymond Scheib, 1965-1967 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Prof. Stanley Schiff, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Tedford E. Schoonover, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Tedford E. Schonover, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Morris G. Shanker, 1979-1983 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Arthur Sempliner, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Sue Olinger Shaw, 1985-1986 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Robert W. Smedley, 1978-1984 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Justin C. Smith, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Prof. Harry F. Stark, 1969-1978 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Arthur L. Stashower, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Donald V. Steger, 1943-1952 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Richard B. Taylor, 1983 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Robert S. Thompson, 1964-1965 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Roger Tilbury, 1986 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Egbert H. Van Delden, 1964-1966 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Pierre Verge, 1936-1974 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - George L. Weasler, 1948 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Irving Weissman, 1955 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Louis A. Whitehair, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Prof. Douglas F. Whitman, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Joseph F. Wildebush, 1953 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Bryan Williams Esq., 1977 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - Anne H. Woolf, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Harold G. Wren, 1979-1992 (Box 20, Folder 62)
- Resigned members before 1987 A-Z. (Box 21)
  - George W. Adams, 1979-1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Edward J. Allen, 1953-1954 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - David C. Altrock, 1963-1977 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Harry W. Arthurs, 1967-1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Lloyd H. Bailer, 1950-1985 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - David M. Beatty, 1976-1982 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Herbert Blumer, 1966-1982 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Walter E. Boles Jr., 1965-1977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Glenn A. Bowers, 1954-1964 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Abner Brodie, 1965-1983 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - W. Roy Buckwalter, 1964-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - John M. Carmody, 1954-1955 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Albert V. Carter, 1983-1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Alfred B. Clark, 1981-1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - William H. Coburn, 1961-1985 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - A. Langley Coffey, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - John R. Coleman, 1959-1967 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - J. Harvey Daly, 1965-1985 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Dudley E. Whiting, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - David R. Douglass, 1951-1974 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Harry T. Edwards, 1972-1984 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Frank D, Emerson, 1962-1966 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Clyde Emery, 1961-1976 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Walter J. Fisher, 1954-1964 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - James Lawrence Fly, 1956 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - William Ray Forrester, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Alexander Hamilton Fray, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Herbert Fuchs, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Lloyd K. Garrison, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Walter Gellhorn, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Lawrence R. Guild, 1953-1976 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Dean Daniel Gutman, 1963-1965 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Paul R. Hays, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - George H. Hildebrand, 1955-1984 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Prof. Louis L. Jaffe, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Vernon H. Jensen, 1954-1981 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Theodore W. Kheel, 1954-1978 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Thomas A. Knowlton, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Melvin Lennard, 1960-1984 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Judge Rene Lippe, 1972-1979 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Joseph D. Lohman, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Louis M. Loeb, 1954 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Edward T. Maslanka Esq., 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Prof. Richard C. Maxwell, 1977-1980 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Perry Meyer, 1972-1984 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Frederick Meyer, 1964-1977 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Earl J. Miller, 1971-1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Morris L. Myers, 1970-1971 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Kenneth E. Norman, 1974-1984 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Thomas L. Norton, 1967 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Reuben Oppenheimer, 1955 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Donald J. O'Shea, 1984 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - George Ostrow, 1956-1984 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Jean-Louis Peloquin, 1973-1979 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Charles F. Penniman, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Orme W. Phelps, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Frank C. Pierson, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Roy R. Ray, 1965-1977 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Herbert W. Rogers, 1950-1958 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Murray M. Rohman, 1963-1978 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Syd N. Rose, 1973-1976 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Eugene Russell, 1961-1962 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Paul H. Sanders, 1976-1984 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - John Thad Scott Jr., 1955-1962 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - John W. Seybold, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Philip Taft, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - John W. Teele, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Arnold R. Weber, 1968-1986 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Paul C. Weiler, 1969-1984 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Bertram F. Willcox, 1956-1983 (Box 21, Folder 70)
- Miscellaneous John Dunford and Gladys Gruendberg history manuscript draft. (Box 22)
  - 1974 Annual Meeting - K.C. Membership Committee (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - 1975 January 17 Pittsburgh - Membership (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Membership Committee Ethics Committee San Francisco 1976 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Membership Committee Puerto Rico April 28, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - K.C. Meet 1973 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Membership Committee Chicago Dec 5, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Special Committee to Review Membership and Related Policy Questions Folder #1, 1975-1993 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Special Committee to Review Membership and Related Policy Questions Folder #2, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - "The NAA a History" Folder #1, 1995-1996 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - "The NAA a History" Folder #2, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - "The NAA a History" Folder #3, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - 1990 Annual Meeting Folder #1 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - 1990 Annual Meeting Folder #2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Board of Governors reports; Newsletters (1967-1971; Chronicle (1974-1996). (Box 23)
  - NAA - The Chronicle, 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #2, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #3, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - NAA - The Chronicle, 1992-1993 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #5, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #6, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #7, 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #8, 1981-1985 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #9, 1979-1981 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - NAA - The Chronicle #10, 1974-1978 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - NAA - Newsletter, 1967-1970 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Minutes of the Board of Governors' Meeting June 1 and 2, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Board of Governors' Meeting October 31, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - NAA - 1987 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - NAA - 1987, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - NAA - 1988 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Minutes of the Board of Governors' Meeting October 26 and 27, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - 1990 Mid-Year Board of Governors' Meeting (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Minutes of the Board of Governors' Meeting, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Minutes of the Board of Governors' Meeting May 27 ands 28, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - 1993 Meetings - NAA (Box 23, Folder 21)
- NAA Arbitration - 1976 (Box 24.1, Folder 1)
- NAA Arbitration - 1977 (Box 24.1, Folder 2)
- Labor Arbitration at the Quarter-Century Mark, 1972 (Box 24.1, Folder 3)
- Arbitration 1985 Law and Practice (Box 24.1, Folder 4)
- Arbitration 1984: Absenteeism, Recent Law Panels, and Published Decisions (Box 24.1, Folder 5)
- The Arbitration the NLRB and the Courts, 1967 (Box 24.1, Folder 6)
- Challenges to Arbitration, 1967 (Box 24.1, Folder 7)
- Arbitration 1991 - The Changing Face of Arbitration in Theory and Practice (Box 24.1, Folder 8)
- Arbitration 1989 (Box 24.1, Folder 9)
- Arbitration 1992 (Box 24.1, Folder 10)
- Developments in American and Foreign Arbitration, 1968 (Box 24.1, Folder 11)
- Arbitration of Subcontracting and Wage Incentive Disputes, 1978-1980 (Box 24.1, Folder 12)
- Arbitration 1993 Arbitration and the Changing World of Work (Box 24.1, Folder 13)
- Arbitration and the Law, 1959 (Box 24.1, Folder 14)
- Arbitration and Social Change, The Arbitrator and the Parties, 1958-1969 (Box 24.2, Folder 1)
- Arbitration and the Expanding role of Neutrals, Arbitration and the Public interest, 1989 (Box 24.2, Folder 2)
- Collective Bargaining and the Arbitrator's Role, Arbitration 1990 New Perspectives on Old Issues (Box 24.2, Folder 3)
- Llabor Arbitration Perspectives and Problems, Arbitration of Interest Disputes, 1973-1974 (Box 24.2, Folder 4)
- The Profession of Labor Arbitration, Arbitration-1974, 1948-1974 (Box 24.2, Folder 5)
- Truth, Lie Detectors, and Other Problems in Labor Arbitration, Arbitration-1975 (Box 24.2, Folder 6)
- Arbitration Issues for the 1980s, Arbitration 1982 Conduct of the Hearing (Box 24.2, Folder 7)
- Arbitration Promise and Performance, Proceedings of the 18th Annual Meeting of the NAA, 1965-1983 (Box 24.2, Folder 8)
- Arbitration 1988 Emerging Issues for the 1990s, Labor Arbitration and Industrial Change, 1963-1988 (Box 24.2, Folder 9)
- Arbitration 1986 Current and Expanding Roles, Arbitration 1987 The Academy at Forty, 1986-1987 (Box 24.2, Folder 10)
- Arbitration and Public Policy, 1961 (Box 24.2, Folder 11)
- Letters - AAA, NAA, 1980-1981 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- NAA Committee on Legal Protection, 1979-1982 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Committee on Legal Representation #2, 1980-1982 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- David E. Feller - Misc., 1953-2003 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Additional Material from Sam Kagel, 2003-2005 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- War Labor Board Skit, 1943 (Box 25, Folder 6)